### ADAM SOUDANI

145 La Crescenta Drive, Camarillo, CA 93010

Ph: (805) 377-2125 asoudani@icloud.com

# **Professional Summary**

Responsibilities in job experience include data entry with Excel and MS office, organizing client investment information, and customer service. Thrives in deadline driven environments where I enjoy collaborating with a team and managing a project from beginning stages to completion. Current Web Development student through UCLA Extension.

#### Skills

- Excel, Powerpoint, and Word
- Node, Firebase

- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript

## **Experience**

Logix Federal Credit Union- Newbury Park, CA

May 2019- February 2020

- Handled loan payments, Wire payments, transfer of funds, mortgage payments, balanced ATM machines and educated members on products and services.
- Assisted with the branch balancing using Excel
- · Performed member call backs to ensure satisfaction and answer questions

Shea Homes- Camarillo/Los Angeles, CA (internship)

October 2018- February 2019

- Worked with community development managers on projects in Ventura and LA counties
- Secured LA county building permits and Certificate of Occupancy Clearances
- Organized and gathered architectural, structural, post tension, energy, mechanical and plumbing plans for city plan checks
- Organized customer interest lists
- Coordinated with engineers, project architects, and contractors to provide correct documents, plans, and signatures required to move projects forward

Fresh Patch-Oxnard, CA

May 2017- September 2017

- · Trained new employees, handled customer complaints, packed and shipped products
- Assisted with company promotional strategies

LPL Financial- Camarillo, CA (internship)

May 2016 - September 2016

- Organized client investment data using Microsoft Office
- Assisted in financial analysis of investments
- Set up and managed paper and electronic filing systems for over 500 clients

#### **Education**

San Diego State University, Bachelors of Arts in Economics September 2014 - May 2018

### **Extracurricular Activities**

Rio Mesa Basketball Camp Counselor, Delta Sigma Phi Fraternity SDSU, Building Industry's HomeAid Volunteer